Hello, it is possible for you to use
AI to automate your course creation process.
And I'm talking about the entire process from
the ideation, getting your video, editing your video,
creating the course structure, publishing your course.
And at the end of the day, the
major work you will do is ensuring that
everything works well.
Just think of it like you're delegating your
task to someone to help you do them.
But this time around, not a human, but
you're relying on machine to help you do
all of those things.
If you watch my previous video, you'll see
how we were able to use AI to
grab video from YouTube, convert that video into
what the AI can understand.
The AI retread the video, split the videos.
And after doing that, it then exported the
video.
I'm going to be showing you some of
those things right now.